oddshot.tv 2016-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Oddshot

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Oddshot Inc. (“we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on www.oddshot.tv (the “Site”), our OddShot browser extensions (each, an “Extension”), and the services, features, content or applications we offer, including your interactions with our social media accounts on Twitter, Twitch, the Oddshot blog and the like (all of the foregoing, collectively, the “Services”). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for Services, through your user account on such Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners. 

The Services are designed to be used by persons over 13 years of age; if you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to use the Services. If we discover that we have collected any Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 we will take appropriate measures to delete such information from our systems.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services, applications, social media sites or platforms (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through or with the Services, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

Use of the Services from outside the U.S., including the European Economic Area, may involve the transfer of Personal Information outside such non-U.S. territories for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that laws in the U.S. may not provide the same level of protection for Personal Information as the laws of your country of residence. If you have any questions about our data processing or transfer practices as it relates to your Personal Information that are not answered in this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@oddshot.tv.

## What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We may collect the following types of information from our users.

### Account Information

If you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as a username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, but only rarely when we feel such information is important. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we, regardless, reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

### User Content

Some features of the Services allow you to provide Content (as defined in our Terms of Service http://oddshot.tv/tos) to the Services. All Content created by you through, or submitted by you to, the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to make available or disclose such Content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal any other of your Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collected Automatically by the Services

  * We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address and cookie information. If you access the Services from your mobile device, we may also automatically collect your mobile device identifier. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on) in order to provide and improve our Services.
  * The Services may also automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site, and information about individual users’ use of the Extensions or interaction with Content, including behavioral data. This type of data enables us and our partners to figure out how and how often individuals use parts of the Services, so that we can analyze, improve, and personalize them for you. 

### Email Communications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service.

### Information Collected Using Cookies

  * Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services through the Internet. 
  * Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with your Account if you have one. 
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you to take advantage the most attractive features of the Services.
  * This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer. 

### Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons

To support and enhance the Services, we may now or in the future serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. 

Advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personal Information (e.g., gender or age), may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. We will not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.

To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

### Aggregate Information

We may collect and aggregate statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This aggregated statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

### Information Regarding Your Social Networks

You can interact with your accounts on other social media services, such as Twitch or Twitter, in connection with your use of the Services. By using uploading, commenting or “sharing” tools on such services, you acknowledge that some account information may be transmitted from that other social media account to us, which information, when received by us, is covered by this Privacy Policy. Additionally, when you use one of these tools, the Third Party Service that operates the tool may be collecting information about your browser or online activity through its own tracking technologies and subject to its own privacy policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other policies of the social networks you use in connection with the Services. 

## How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?

The Services are designed to help you share Content with others. As a result, some Content generated through the Services is shared publicly or with third parties.

### Public Information About Your Activity on the Services

Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, Content you have posted publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services. Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. Unregistered users will not have this association, but information concerning their use of the Services (such as what pages they have visited) may be tracked anonymously through the use of cookies and stored by us. 

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information publicly, including by using certain public features of the Services or creating a public profile, then individuals reading such Content may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that Content. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem to be private in Content that you create or submit through the Services.

### IP Address Information

While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy. 

### Information You Elect to Share

You may access other Third Party Services through or in connection with use of the Services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected by the Services.

### Aggregate Information

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

### Email Communications with Us

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications relating to your Account. Communications relating to your Account will only be sent for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery.

### User Profile Information

User profile information including your username and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services. We will not directly reveal user email addresses to other users.

### Information Shared with Our Agents

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide the Services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

### Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

### Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety and that of our partners, our users, and the public. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud and infringement protection and spam/malware prevention.

### Information We Share With Your Consent

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

## Is Information About Me Secure? 

We store information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise. If you have an Account, you need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account (and Personal Information contained therein) by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

## What Information of Mine Can I Access?

Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information, which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 8547 E Arapahoe Rd, Ste J #455 Greenwood Village, CO 80112, United States.

## How Can I Delete My Account? 

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing help@oddshot.tv. If you terminate your Account, any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your Account. However, given the nature of sharing on the Services, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion, and all Content, will remain stored on our servers and accessible to the public.

## What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

  * You can use many of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.
  * You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some of our features. If you believe your intellectual property or personal rights (other than your copyright rights) have been infringed by another User, please review our Intellectual Property and DMCA Copyright Policy (http://oddshot.tv/dmca) and our Oddshot Opt Outs policy in our Terms of Service (http://oddshot.tv/tos), or contact us at legal@oddshot.tv.
  * You can delete your Account. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity and Content generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible. 

## What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

## What If I Have Questions or Concerns? 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to legal@oddshot.tv. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: October 2015
